It's nice having so many friendly faces
around. I'm so used to training on my
own.
>> That sounds just like my life before
Mecca. Sweating it out at the PC bang.
>> Were you just gaming?
>> Hey, esports are still sports.
>> There was a tea leaf standing up in my
cup this morning. That means good luck,
right?
>> Not if you tell me.
You ruined it for yourself.
>> Papa, have you seen a delivery of cat
litter? I've been looking all over. You
mean the clumping low dust moisture
absorbing sand? It was perfect for
cleaning up those pesky oil stains.
>> Pa,
[laughter]
>> I'm joking. I'll keep an eye out for it.
>> Brigittita, if you were me, how would
you make a good impression on the team?
>> Oh, that's easy. Just let them try on
your hat.
>> That's pretty good. Wait, you're
serious? Well, it worked for Cassidy, so
I'd say it's worth a shot.
>> When I visit Genji in Japan, I better
not find him hacked to pieces again.
>> If you do, it will not have been by my
hand.
>> So, you let someone else hack him up
instead? [sighs]
>> That was not what I meant.
>> Deadlock's really tearing a path across
the West these days.
Appreciate the enthusiasm, Bastion, but
I don't think I'm the right man to stop
him.
>> What's wrong, cowboy? You miss Genji
that bad?
>> He ain't the only one. Got a lot of old
friends out there I've been thinking
about lately.
>> You're not trapped here, Cole. I know
you'd be doing good wherever you end up.
>> That makes one of us. But nice of you to
say. That new blade is rather bold,
darling.
>> Designed to terrify, is it?
>> Of course. I always like to leave a
lasting impression. I commend you, Vera.
Your company's shielding has proven
quite useful so far. Of course, paired
with those new armaments, your victory
is all but assured. When Vishka
rebuilds, I expect a monument to my
leadership. Consider it done, my dear.
Life's been too easy lately. Maybe I
ought to give your bounty a try.
>> Good luck with that.
>> Thank you for lending us your aid,
Commander. Let us sit down for tea the
next time you visit.
>> I'll take you up on that. As long as we
go somewhere that does the roasted
stuff. Those dragons available to rent?
>> Absolutely not.
>> I want them swirling around the new Junk
City Arena. A proper light show for when
we crown our champs.
>> Then have your foolish lackey set off
their little fireworks.
>> Keep pushing omnics around and the
freaks will be coming for you.
>> Who are you?
>> I'm about to be the thorn in your side,
big boy.
>> That's pig boy to you.
>> I always see you with that smiling
onion.
>> Yeah, what about it?
>> Nothing. I think it's cute.
Same.
>> My biggest dream is to set off a
fantastical explosion, incinerate
everything and everyone as the place IS
BLOWN TO SMITHERINES. What do you think?
>> I think that sounds like a nightmare.
>> Will you lot stop blasting my ship?
You've been a real pain in my kidneys.
We'll start blasting your ship when you
stop invading Busousan. Well, that's no
fair at all. It's time to make him
bleed, Gracie.
Oh,
>> what? Your name's Gracie, too. Funny.
You look more like a carnage.
>> Our little vacation's coming up, boys.
Don't make me regret bringing you.
>> We never, my queen. I'll cover every
grain OF SAND WITH EXPLOSIVES. BOOM.
>> Bloody idiots. They might let a bot run
things around here, but Junker Town
would rip you to shreds.
Huh? If I ever leave Japan, your little
garbage pile is the last place I'd
visit. Do not forget our terms. I won't
allow your recklessness to ruin my
plans. You doubting me, lady?
>> I made a kingdom out of wreckage.
>> And wreckage suits you. Just don't burn
down what I've built. Doomfist. Doom
fist.
It's a great name. What's yours?
>> They call me Jungrat.
>> Not as good.
>> No, not as good. 1 2 3 4. No, wait. Wait
for it.
>> Not this again.
>> Five, six, DEPED [laughter]
to your little patches here. Think
they'll have that limited edition piggy
murray?
>> Hope so.
Then you'll have it, my dear bosom
friend. I'll even threaten the shopkeep
if I have to.
>> Thanks.
>> WE'RE DOING IT, MO. WE'VE GOT A SHIP.
We've got a dream. AND WE'RE SEEING the
world.
>> Yep.
>> Where to next? One of them temples in
Beijing, the sunlit shores of Santorini,
or maybe maybe even Missouri.
>> Ooh, Missouri. If the pot was sweet
enough, I might be willing to serve you.
Madam Wolf,
>> I have no use for the allegiance of once
so willing to betray his leaders.
>> Who said anything about betrayal? I was
only TALKING ABOUT TEAMS FISHERADES.
>> YOU and old Mako seem to be having a
good time out here enjoying the
patchimaris.
>> That we are. The sound of those sweet
little onions are a sonorfic symphony to
my eard drums. Like when you squeeze
him?
>> No, like when we bum the whole machine.
>> By the way, Chikasa says she forgives
you.
>> Does anyone else?
>> You know the answer to that.
>> Well, thanks for letting me know.
>> When I think of what you put Mizuki
through, I feel sick to my stomach.
>> Oh, my little Opakun.
You should focus on what he put you
through instead. That story about losing
your arm in a bike accident. Was that a
lie, too?
>> Not entirely. There was a bike involved.
>> Still skirting around the details, huh?
>> I'm not trying to hide anything, Kiko.
It's just really hard to talk about.
>> Was there ever a world where you'd have
sold us out?
>> No, I realized pretty quick I could
never betray you guys. I'm glad Toltoan
is safe now, but I wish we didn't have
to blow up his forge. He'll find a way
to keep up his craft.
>> But that building held all his secrets.
>> No, he does. Isn't that why you guys
bothered keeping him alive?
>> Will you thank Novata for letting me
keep that?
>> It's fine. Not like he would have made
you give it back.
>> He doesn't want to hear from me, does
he?
>> Can you blame him? You know what the
Hashimoto did to his sister?
>> You did some good work against the
Hashimoto out there.
>> Thanks. Didn't hurt having Commander
Chase backing me up. Well, if you ever
want to take that fox sightseeing, you'd
be welcome in Overwatch.
>> Nice of you to offer, but I think I'm
right where I want to be.
>> Funny that guys with no loyalties keep
ending up at Overwatch.
>> Guys, you mean it's not just me?
>> Oh, did I say that? Slip of the tongue.
>> Why have you forsaken me? I taught you
strength. I gave you a reason to live.
>> No. Tolshan and the Yo-kai did.
>> You think they still care for you after
what you did? It's not too late to
return to my side.
>> Never. I made my choice. And it wasn't
you.
>> Muki. Mizuki.
When I get my hands on you, whatever
shall I put you through?
>> Your words don't scare me anymore.
>> And what of my actions? How much pain
does that body of yours remember? Not as
much as yours will if you come after me.
>> Genji made a strong case for you,
recruit. Don't let him down.
>> I won't. Not when you're all giving me
another chance at life.
>> Even in her own keep, Shiion could not
lead the Hashimoto to victory. How
beautiful.
>> Better not let her hear you talking like
that. She's killed for a lot less.
>> She could not bust me. Rage as mindless
as hers is a weakness I've long since
overcome.
>> Uh-huh. Whatever you say.
>> Hey, you knew the champ.
>> Oh, you mean Hammond? Yes. We were
friends on a lunar colony.
>> Not what he said.
>> I just know there's something terrible
under that mask of yours.
None of your business,
>> silly little piggy.
Everything I want is my business. Of all
your queen's pawns, you seem the most
cutthroat.
>> I ain't her porn.
>> Perhaps not. But she plays you all the
same. Hey, uh you um you really you're
tall.
>> [laughter]
>> Oh, wow. And you're funny, too.
>> Yep.
>> Since you're handling Mizuki now, you
should know that his performance will
suffer if he is cuddled.
>> I don't need him to perform. Overwatch
isn't a circus.
>> Oh, [laughter]
you could have fooled me.
>> You must be ashamed. Losing that boy to
Overwatch. I suppose the Hashimoto do
not value filthy as I do. They can have
his loyalty for all I care. As long as I
control his fear, he's still mine.
>> Prepare yourself, Subject Sigma. I will
have need of you soon.
>> How soon is when time slips away? When
moments become millennia,
>> enough. Dr. Adiran will harness your
power when the time is right.
>> The harness. Yes, of course.
>> Kind of nice not being the new kid
anymore, huh?
I wasn't calling you a kid. Wait, how
old are you?
>> Reckon Busousan's in need of a little
fireworks show?
>> The only fireworks show you'll see will
be my missiles blowing up in your face.
>> In the mood to follow my orders today,
Song.
>> If those orders involve me wrecking the
bad guys? You bet. [laughter]
>> I'll see what I can do. Hey gamers, I'm
Uni
>> and I'm Hana Song
>> and together we'll be hosting my Mecca
Mania. You may know Mecca Squad as top
competitors, but this time we'll be
turning the tables and competing against
each other.
>> Each other.
>> Oh, you heard right. Players will vote
between all five Mecca Squad members to
see who's this year's top Mecca talent.
And for the record, I'm not losing to
anyone. Not even you, Hana.
>> Huh? We'll see about that. I know I'm
not going down easy, but neither are
king, casino, or overlord.
>> Just the way I like it. Well, players,
get voting.
>> Game on.
>> Div.A is our leading ace. Familiar
feeling for you?
>> What can I say? Old habits die hard.
>> Demon is in the lead. Wait, it's kind of
embarrassing reading my name off the
prompter like that. That's nothing to be
embarrassed about, Anie. But if I beat
you, different story.
>> Yeah. Yeah. King is king of the votes.
It's just like him to push his way to
the top.
>> Like how he pushes his glasses up his
face cuz he might just slide back down,
too.
>> How did you even come up with that
visual? Casinos raced his way to the
top. Think our speedster can keep the
lead?
>> Not if I can help it. A win's on the
line and I'm not staying in my lane.
Overlord is in the lead. Our youngest
member never messes around.
>> Doesn't mean we'll go easy on him,
right?
>> Never. This is just a halfway point. But
a real pro knows that a match isn't over
till it's over.
>> That's all for our Mid Mania update.
Keep those votes coming.
>> This is it. The votes have been counted.
The results are locked in.
>> And now for the moment we've all been
waiting for. The winner of my mecha
mania is drum roll
demon.
Hey, would you look at that?
>> Wow, you did it on me. That's our Mecca
leader.
>> Casino.
Not sure he'll care, though.
>> Come on, Yuna. Even someone as cool as
him will have to crack a smile for this
award.
>> King, [laughter]
we'll never hear the end of this, will
we?
>> That's what happens when you feed a
troll. He earned it, though. Overlord.
Aw, look at him go. I'm proud of him.
>> Woohoo. That's what I call a Mecca
Mangna moment.
>> Thanks for joining us on this season of
My Mecca Mania.
>> See you in game. Waiting me.
Another win in the bag.
>> Glad to see things haven't changed too
much, Hana.
>> Oh, that one's always going missing.
Picked the wrong side, sweetheart. I'll
help Ephere rebuild you later.
>> Is that a skill issue? I do regret that
a little.
>> You don't deserve my loyalty.
>> The swiftness of the blade matters more
than its size. Your harmony has been
broken. Walk not between light and dark.
Each light cast a shadow.
>> Did your mother not teach you caution?
>> It's not all fun in games.
>> Look at me flying around like what's her
name? YOU MIGHT BE THE BOSS, BUT I'M THE
QUEEN. Better leave it to the grown-ups,
kid. Back to the alley, you mog.
Another metal demon down.
Just fun and games, Wolfie. Shattered.
You a mountain or a molehill?
>> Wonder if I can salvage those tires. He
can't keep that eye off me. Business is
booming. Nice try, big guy. JUNKRAT ONE.
MECCA negative one.
Hate to let down a fan.
>> My llamas now. I'm the big guy here.
Fresh scrap. Not your piggy. Quit
staring.
Hairballs.
All talk.
Binks [clears throat] can fly.
You're not catching me.
>> He is the superior mech pilot. He is the
real beast around here.
>> You have a mech and I still won. Someone
forgot to warm up. Out of your element.
Beast really doesn't like you. Go touch
grass. Beast beats wolf. What happened
superstar? It's tough love, bestie.
Maybe next time, champ.
That's enough jumping around.
Should have seen that coming. Hana can't
hack if you're dead. Your speedrun's
over. Nobody wants your hamster clutter.
You're washed. All that hacking and you
still lost. Shooting star comes crashing
down. And don't come back. I've missed
having you around, Genji. You've still
got it. Nice shot, Hana. You swim well
with a current. [clears throat]
>> Neat trick, bat.
>> Never thought I'd be watching your back.